<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A Map The Size Of Paris</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A Map The Size Of Paris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 17:42:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/pastpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 17:42:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/pastpapers/</guid>
      <description>Publications Timing and Shape of Stochastic Autocatalytic Burst Formation,
A. Jamieson-Lane &amp;amp; E. Cytrnbaum. Chaos, 2019.
Deterministic and Stochastic Modeling of the MinSystem for Cell Division,
A. Jamieson-Lane, UBC PhD thesis, 2019
AnthroTools: An R Package for Cross-Cultural Ethnographic Data Analysis
B.G. Purzycki &amp;amp; A. Jamieson-Lane, Cross-Cultural Research, 2017
Localized Spot Patterns on the Sphere for Reaction-Diffusion Systems: Theory and Open Problems
A. Jamieson-Lane, P. Trinh &amp;amp; M. Ward (book chapter in Mathematical and Computational Approaches in Advancing Modern Science and Engineering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact and CV</title>
      <link>https://example.com/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/aboutme/</guid>
      <description> Contact information: Email: alastair.jamieson-lane@uni-oldenburg.de
Office: W15-1-145
Mail address:
Campus Wechloy, Gebäude W15 Carl-von-Ossietzky-Straße 9 - 11 26111 Oldenburg Germany  Curriculum Vitae </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://example.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/research/</guid>
      <description>Current Research Currently, I am working with the University of Oldenburg and UMCG in Groningen, studying the evolution and spread of antibiotic resistance. My most recent projects are focused on studying how horizontal gene transfer effects evolutionary dynamics in microbes, and how knowledge of network structure (on a variety of scales) can be used to predict and control the spread of infections.
Past Research Pattern Formation In the Min System Symmetry breaking and pattern formation are critical to the existence of complex life in the world around us, and have fascinated researchers for many years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://example.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description> For Students I am not currently teaching.
Previously I have taught:
 Multivariate Calculus at University of British Columbia
 Derivative Calculus for Life Scientist at University of British Columbia
 Derivative Calculus for Physical Sciences and Engineering at University of British Columbia
 STAR course (University mathematics for highschool students) at University of Canterbury (NZ)
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>