<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A Map The Size Of Paris</title>
    <link>https://alastair-jl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A Map The Size Of Paris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 17:42:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alastair-jl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://alastair-jl.github.io/pastpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 17:42:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alastair-jl.github.io/pastpapers/</guid>
      <description>Publications The Gossip Paradox: why do bacteria share genes?,
A. Jamieson-Lane &amp;amp; B. Blasius. Submitted to arXiv, Dec 2020; accepted for publication in Mathematical Biosciences and Engineering.
Comparing optimization criteria in antibiotic allocation protocols,
A. Jamieson-Lane, A. Friedrich &amp;amp; B. Blasius Royal Society Open Science
Calculation of epidemic arrival time distributions using branching processes,
A. Jamieson-Lane &amp;amp; B. Blasius. Physical Review E, 2020.
Effects of age-targeted sequestration for COVID-19,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact and CV</title>
      <link>https://alastair-jl.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alastair-jl.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description> Contact information: Email: alastair.jamieson-lane@auckland.ac.nz
Office: 220-303
Mail address:
Second floor, Building 303 The University of Auckland, 38 Princes Street Auckland CBD, Auckland 1010 New Zealand  Curriculum Vitae </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Research</title>
      <link>https://alastair-jl.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alastair-jl.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Past Research Pattern Formation In the Min System Symmetry breaking and pattern formation are critical to the existence of complex life in the world around us, and have fascinated researchers for many years.
A particularly beautiful example of this is the Min system for cell division, in which the regulatory proteins MinD and MinE ensure cell division down the midline of the cell through a ``chase and release&amp;rdquo; mechanism that inhibits cell division near either cell pole (depicted right).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://alastair-jl.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alastair-jl.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching I am currently teaching:
 Partial Differential Equations at University of Auckland
 Inverse Problems and Stochastic Differential Equations at University of Auckland
  If you are in either of those courses, go check out their canvas pages.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also been running virtual tutorials in Gather.town.
By the looks of it, we&amp;rsquo;ll be back on campus in person soon, so you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to attend tutorials in person.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>